<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Landing Page on Princeton COS Undergraduate Course Assistants Program</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/</link><description>Recent content in Landing Page on Princeton COS Undergraduate Course Assistants Program</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Jobs &amp; Why Do Them</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/jobs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/jobs/</guid><description>These are the jobs available.
To be changed # From registration form:
The Department of Computer Science hires undergraduates to assist (as grader and/or as lab TA and/or as facilitator) with many &amp;gt; COS courses. Lab TAs are undergraduates hired to work in the computer labs to help students taking COS 126, 217, and 226 (the &amp;gt; Intro COS Lab). This web form will allow you to apply for any of these positions.</description></item><item><title>Recruiting UCAs for Spring 2023</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2022-12-02-recruiting-ucas-for-spring-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2022-12-02-recruiting-ucas-for-spring-2023/</guid><description>The TigerUHR campaign for Spring 2023 will open at the end of January 2023, when everyone&amp;rsquo;s term schedules is clearer.
If you want to be kept in the loop, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to fill-in this notice of interest. This will let us know to reach out to you directly when applications for Spring 2023 open up.
Please note that it is important to submit this notice of interest even if you have worked us, as we may not automatically contact previously hired UCAs (for no particular reason other that we don&amp;rsquo;t want to spam people).</description></item><item><title>COS Lab Recruiting for Fall 2021</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2021-08-13-cos-lab-recruiting-for-fall-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2021-08-13-cos-lab-recruiting-for-fall-2021/</guid><description>Today we sent the following announcement to all COS undergraduate students, with broader diffusion of this message to follow:
Hello, and I hope your summer is going well!
The Department of Computer Science is hiring enrolled undergraduates (that&amp;rsquo;s you!) to assist in many of our COS courses as Undergraduate Course Assistants (UCAs). This is an opportunity to gain teaching experience, work with and get to know faculty, and contribute back to our undergraduate curriculum.</description></item><item><title>Launching the New Site</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2021-07-29-launch-of-site/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2021-07-29-launch-of-site/</guid><description>This is a website to document the valuable contribution that undergraduate students provide the teaching mission of Princeton University&amp;rsquo;s Deparment of Computer Science, and to provide information on this program.
The goal of the website will be, among other things, to help provide information to both prospective applicants and current students about the different roles and jobs fulfilled by Undergraduate Course Assistants.
The website is built using the Hugo static site generator, the Hugo Book theme, and is hosted on GitHub Pages.</description></item><item><title>Before Getting Paid...</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/payroll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/payroll/</guid><description>Overview # Before getting paid by the Department of Computer Science, you need to be registered in two different places:
You need to be registered with the Student Employment Office to be added to university payroll: They will check your eligibility to work, and collect the necessary tax forms. This is a necessary step for any job on campus, but must only be done once during your time at Princeton.</description></item><item><title>Past Helpers</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/general/past-ucas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/general/past-ucas/</guid><description>This page lists past employees.
Past Head Lab TAs # In chronological order, since 2013:
Alex Daifotis Erica Portnoy and Utsarga Sikder Curtis Belmont Diana Liao Sally Jiao Benjamin G. Schiffer Justin Chang and Lily Zhang Julia Ruskin Past Tool Builders # Vinay Ayyala &amp;lsquo;16 (codePost) Alex Daifotis &amp;lsquo;14 (LabQueueV1) James Evans &amp;lsquo;16 (codePost) Richard Freling &amp;lsquo;16 (codePost) Lance Goodridge ’17 *19 (TigerUHR and LabQueueV3)</description></item><item><title>How to Contribute to this Site</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/general/contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/general/contribute/</guid><description>How to Contribute to this Site # This site is hosted in a public GitHub repository. It uses the Hugo static site generator and the actual pages are written in Markdown (see cheat sheet here). It is published using GitHub Pages.
Anybody with a GitHub account, can suggest changes to an existing page with only two or three clicks, like for Wikipedia. (Anybody can also propose new pages, but that requires a few more clicks.</description></item><item><title>How to Declare Your Hours</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/time-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/time-collection/</guid><description>Princeton University uses JobX to advertise and solicit applications for most student employment jobs on campus (recruiting both undergraduate and graduate students). These jobs are typically hourly jobs, and student employees declare their hours on TimesheetX. Below is information on how to use the latter to declare your hours for COS jobs.
For most UCA jobs, the Department of Computer Science does its hiring through TigerUHR. However some jobs, in particular summer research internships, are advertised through JobX.</description></item><item><title>How/When to Apply</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/apply/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/apply/</guid><description>This is a page to explain how/when to apply. To be written.
Applications are submitted on the TigerUHR registration page.
Transcript Information # As part of the application process, TigerUHR will ask that you submit an up-to-date transcript. These documents can be obtained from TigerHub.
Internal Transcript # Also acceptable: Degree Progress Report #</description></item><item><title>Jobs that Require An Interview</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/interview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/interview/</guid><description>Some jobs require an interview, currently this includes the following jobs:
COS 126 Lab TA COS 2xx Lab TA Because scheduling and giving interviews takes time, these jobs usually have an earlier deadline than most jobs.
Information about the COS Lab Interview Process # Julia Ruskin BSE &amp;lsquo;22, Head Lab TA in 2021, describes the interview process for the Intro COS Lab in the following way:
We interview to get a sense for how the candidates would act when interacting with students.</description></item><item><title>The UCA Slack</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/slack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/employees/slack/</guid><description>The Slack is where certain jobs coordinate.</description></item></channel></rss>