<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>**For Prospective Applicants** on Princeton COS Undergraduate Course Assistants Program</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/</link><description>Recent content in **For Prospective Applicants** on Princeton COS Undergraduate Course Assistants Program</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COS UCA Job Catalog</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/jobs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/jobs/</guid><description>This page provides a general description of the responsibilities of all the jobs that are available to UCAs in Princeton University&amp;rsquo;s Department of Computer Science. It also provides a description of the different job categories.
General Job Categories # The department employs undergraduates to assist with many COS courses. The jobs are divided into three categories (most paid $18.92/hr):
Lab TAs who help students in undergraduate-staffed office hours Graders who grade assignments and (in some courses) exams In-class TAs who help students in the classroom (these positions are called facilitators or precept assistants) Some Independent Work (IW) seminars also hires 1-2 UCAs to do a combination of all three jobs (assisting in class to provide feedback to student presenting their projects, grading projects, and providing office hours for students to get help with their projects).</description></item><item><title>Rules for Choosing a Job</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/choice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/choice/</guid><description>Every semester, the Department of Computer Science processes about over 500 applications, for more than 250 positions (some UCAs work in several positions). We are very grateful for the interest in our courses, and we are committed to providing a fair and transparent process for all applicants.
Our promise to you is to ensure that our process is free from bias and provides every student an opportunity to work in an interesting, résumé-building job, as expected of us by the official guidance set forth by the Office of the Dean of the College.</description></item><item><title>How/When to Apply</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/apply/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/apply/</guid><description>The deparement will send all COS undergraduate students an email with instructions for UCA application about 2 weeks before the start of the semester.
Applications are submitted on the TigerUHR registration page.
Transcript Information # As part of the application process, TigerUHR will ask that you submit an up-to-date transcript. These documents can be obtained from TigerHub.
Internal Transcript # Also acceptable: Degree Progress Report #</description></item><item><title>Jobs that Require An Interview</title><link>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/interview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/docs/applicants/interview/</guid><description>Some jobs require an interview, currently this includes the following jobs:
COS 126 Lab TA COS 2xx Lab TA Because scheduling and giving interviews takes time, these jobs usually have an earlier deadline than most jobs.
Information about the COS Lab Interview Process # Julia Ruskin BSE &amp;lsquo;22, Head Lab TA in 2021, describes the interview process for the Intro COS Lab in the following way:
We interview to get a sense for how the candidates would act when interacting with students.</description></item></channel></rss>